<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">I feel disappointed that I am not becoming the caregiver I wanted to be.</statement>
     <statement id="2">No matter how hard I work, it can feel like it is not enough.</statement>
     <statement id="3">Poor patient outcomes make me question if I belong in this job.</statement>
     <statement id="4">I think about difficult situations, wishing I had handled them better.</statement>
     <statement id="5">I feel guilty when I make quick choices under stress.</statement>
     <statement id="6">A heavy workload stops me from spending more time with patients and their families.</statement>
     <statement id="7">Even when I follow every rule, I can still feel guilt.</statement>
     <statement id="8">I worry that I do not meet the standards of my profession.</statement>
     <statement id="9">Choosing which patient gets care when supplies are low makes me feel guilty.</statement>
     <statement id="10">Small mistakes stay on my mind for a long time.</statement>
     <statement id="11">Asking coworkers to do extra work can make me feel guilty.</statement>
     <statement id="12">I am not sure my work really helps patients.</statement>
     <statement id="13">I often know the right thing, but cannot do it.</statement>
     <statement id="14">I fear my mistakes show I am not good enough.</statement>
     <statement id="15">Promises of help that never come feel dishonest.</statement>
     <statement id="16">When I have too much work, I leave out important aspects in patient care.</statement>
     <statement id="17">I feel powerless when laws conflict with my medical judgment.</statement>
     <statement id="18">I fear backlash if I report wrongdoing.</statement>
     <statement id="19">I have kept quiet to protect my job.</statement>
     <statement id="20">I feel let down by the health system during ethical problems.</statement>
     <statement id="21">I feel bad for not giving more comfort to patients.</statement>
     <statement id="22">Repeated moral problems at work made me doubt my beliefs.</statement>
     <statement id="23">I feel betrayed when leaders make decisions that go against our values.</statement>
     <statement id="24">I have lost trust in coworkers who violate ethical rules.</statement>
     <statement id="25">Rules at work sometimes clash with what I believe is right.</statement>
     <statement id="26">I feel betrayed when policies harm staff well-being.</statement>
     <statement id="27">I sometimes act against my conscience just to keep the peace.</statement>
     <statement id="28">I question the meaning of my life and whether I truly help patients when I see them suffer.</statement>
     <statement id="29">Seeing constant tragedy left me spiritually tired.</statement>
     <statement id="30">I feel I lose my values when I do things I believe are wrong.</statement>
     <statement id="31">I feel disappointed when patient care suffers because we do not have enough resources or time.</statement>
     <statement id="32">My work sometimes conflicts with my sense of purpose and meaning of life.</statement>
     <statement id="33">I feel upset when I see coworkers do something I think is wrong.</statement>
     <statement id="34">I have followed orders that went against my own values.</statement>
     <statement id="35">I still think about times I stayed quiet when something felt wrong.</statement>
     <statement id="36">I feel upset when I stay silent in tough situations.</statement>
     <statement id="37">I feel upset when efficiency rules harm patient care.</statement>
     <statement id="38">I struggle to match my role with my ideals of kindness and fairness.</statement>
     <statement id="39">I feel distant from my spiritual beliefs after making difficult decisions about patient care.</statement>
   </statements>
